The Snow-Capped Present
No way! I refuse!
Whenever we do homework together, you just copy my answers.
You'd better do it by yourself for once!
Shizuka.
Shizuka-chan is very cold to me from few days.
Now I'm so worried...
About what?
Doraemon
I'll get married with Shizuka in the future, right?
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe? What do you mean?
I mean if there isn't any accident take place.
How can it be?
We're in a tight spot now.
I always wondered
How can Shizuka fall in love with Nobita?
There are so many better boys out there!
Right?
Watch what you speak!
Sorry...
Fine..
Time TV.
14 years from now, on October 25th, you get engaged.
So let's look few days earlier...
This is the future you.
I'm so clumsy.
That's Shizuka.
Make up your mind!
Are you coming with me or not?
Well, I'd love to.
But I hate climbing
If the hill was flat...
You need to grow up.
Forget it.
I'll ask others to go with me.
I don't wanna watch it any more. Take up the speed.
Yi?
Shizuka was alone...
She walks apart from her partners due to the blizzard.
What is Nobita doing now?
He's got a fever.
Jeez.
Wait, yeah.
I see.
Machine Cat, lent me your Time Package.
Sure.
What do you want to do?
Don't ask me. You'll know the answer. Keep watching.
You became 14 years older.
And then...
I'm going to rescue Shizuka by the Time Machine.
Well, Shizuka will be deeply affected by me.
You're brave, Nobita.
I'll save you at all costs.
Shizuka, I'm so happy.
Because of this, she'll marry me with pleasure.
Look, don't involve into this case to help me.
I intend to do that by myself.
See you.
Shizuka...
She's there.
Hey, Shizuka.
Nobita.
Shizuka, are you all right?
Why did you come here?
I came here for you. Don't worry.
Leave the bag to me.
No, I can't.
Don't worry. Give it to me.
I can handle it by myself.
Don't walk around after you suffered the blizzard.
You should confirm the direction by the map.
You brought the map, right?
That's your true self.
We can rely on the Polaris to identify the direction. Don't worry.
Great.
It's a cave there. Let's go in to have a rest.
Okay.
The most terrible thing to the guy who suffered blizzard is the cold weather.
Let's make a fire to warm ourselves.
I'll be in charge of making the fire.
Jeez. I can't make it.
I've got a lighter, you wanna try it.
You've got a lighter? Of course.
Because you're working hard, so I don't want to bother you.
It's so cold.
Put on this cloth. Don't worry about me.
This cloth is wet.
How could you wear these clothes to the jokul?
You clothes have become wet. Take off them.
But...
You'll die if you don't take off them.
But I don't have other clothes.
I'll give you my blanket.
Thanks.
I've brought lots of food to eat.
Really? Great.
You brought so many cans, but you forget to bring the can opener, right?
Yeah, you're right.
I've got some solid food. Eat it.
I think he must be exhausted now.
Be careful. It's a slippery ground here.
I broke my leg. And I lost my glasses.
I can't walk any more.
I've asked for the succor.
They'll be here soon. Cheer up.
How is it going?
Oh, no. It's all over.
How can it be?
I don't want to watch it any more.
I'd like to marry Nobita.
Thank you.
If I don't stay with you, I'll worry about you.
I don't want to be a trashy guy.
So you should make a man of yourself.